Izzy’s voicemail: I’m sorry.
I can’t take your call at the moment.
Please leave a message and I’ll get back to you.
Ben: Hi, Izzy.
It’s Ben.
Can you call me back, please?
Receptionist: Light on London.
How can I help you?
Ben: Hi.
Can I speak to Izzy Silva, please?
Receptionist: Just a second, I’ll put you through…
Ben: Izzy?
Receptionist: Sorry, she’s not at her desk right now.
Ben: Can I leave a message, please?
Receptionist: Sure.
Ben: Can you tell her Ben called?
I’ll call her back later.
Receptionist: No problem, I’ll give her the message.
Ben: Thanks.
Receptionist: Light on London, how can I help you?
Ben: Hi.
Can I speak to Izzy Silva, please?
Receptionist: Just a second… I’m sorry, the line’s busy.
Do you want to hold?
Ben: Yes.
I’ll hold.
Max: Hello, Izzy Silva’s phone.
Ben: Uh…Is Izzy there?
Max: Ben?
Er, no.
She’s taken the day off.
Er…I’d give her some space if I were you.
Ben: Thanks for the advice.